How do you feel like tourism at this point is either helping or hurting the Caribbean?
Yeah, I think we have an over-dependency on it.
And COVID taught us that.
And, you know, looking at how we are willing to risk our own health to accommodate tourists, because that is our bread and butter.
I think that was very illuminating for us.
And yes, we even though we still have this connection to the land, I still think that we are having this first world disconnect.
Because, of course, now we're on Instagram.
I'm seeing so-and-so is enjoying themselves and is popping this and that.
And me going to work the land?
Me, I want to go and work in a nice office job and thing or manage like a nice hotel and whatever.
So a lot of us are disconnecting from the land.
Our food import bill and then, you know, having to accommodate these foreign tastes because of tourists, they want strawberries and they want continental breakfast and they want this or whatever.
And then it's like, it is, it is to me a huge detriment.
And I think if we don't do it properly, there's a way to keep a balance.